GENEVIEVE PERRON MIGNERON

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

INFO@GEN-MIGNERON.COM

MONTREAL, QC

I am a front end developer with about 7 years of experience. In the past 4 years, I've been evolving in a Rails environment, while using modern JavaScript frameworks such as React and Angular on the front-end side. I am familiar with unit testing, as well as continuous integration tools.

SKILLS

Frontend HTML (HAML, slim, erb) CSS (SASS, SCSS, LESS) JavaScript (Angular, React, Vue)

Backend Ruby PHP C#

General

Version control systems (Git, SVN, TFS) CI/CD tools Unit testing

EXPERIENCE

GOLO Mobile inc.

Frontend developer September 2019

- Building and maintaining our internal tools, as well as the main website.
- · Working in an agile environment

Hydrogène Solutions Web

Frontend developer May 2019

- Building our internal design system on Vue.js
- Developing and maintaining different websites and platforms for our clients.

Glossier

Frontend Engineer March 2017 - December 2018

- Building new features for the company's website
- Implementing GDPR compliance
- Ensuring the website's compliance with accessibility standards
- Write and receive constructive code reviews
- · Working in an agile environment

Dynamo

Frontend Engineer December 2014 - March 2017

- Maintaining and improving websites previously built by the company
- Building websites from scratch while following W3C standards and ensuring crossbrowser compatibility

Defacto Interactif

Junior Frontend developer August 2013 - September 2014

- Maintaining and improving websites previously built by the company
- Building websites from scratch with Umbraco and Sitecore as a CMS
- Building Facebook contests using their API
- Creating custom newsletter templates

EDUCATION

Maisonneuve College

2010-2012

Technique d'integration multimedia